[{"question": " can i see the comics?", "answer": " this is the new york times.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " guys. i thought you were taking ross to the game?", "answer": " we are. he\u0092s meeting us here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " no! rachel is meeting us here.", "answer": " oh come on, they can be in the same room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yeah, you shoulda been there last night.", "answer": " why? what happened now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " well ross was hangin\u0092 out over at our place, rachel comes over to borrow some moisturiser from chandler....", "answer": " yeah y-you, how hard is it to say something? rachel came over to borrow something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " anyway! her and ross just started yelling at each other.", "answer": " wait. why was he yelling at her? he\u0092s the one who slept with someone else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well, i guess he says that because they were on a break when it happened, that she should of forgiven him by now.", "answer": " whoa!! he is soo unreasonable! god, although i think i understand what he means. oh my god, this is like 60 minutes, okay, when, when, at first you\u0092re really mad at that pharmaceutical company for making the drug and then y'know you just feel bad for the people because they needed to make their hair grow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " y'know what this is like? this is like when my parents got divorced. man, i hope ross doesn\u0092t try to kidnap me after cub scouts.", "answer": " y'know i had a dream where ross and rachel were still together, they never broke up. and we were all just like hanging out, and everyone was happy....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i had the same dream!", "answer": " yeah, and nobody slept with that xerox girl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " oh, i had the opposite dream.", "answer": " y'know what maybe it\u0092s gonna be okay, i mean it\u0092s been a week.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah, i mean it\u0092s never taken me a week to get over a relationship.", "answer": " it\u0092s never taken you more than a shower to get over a relationship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  okay, let\u0092s go!! let\u0092s hit the road!!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " let\u0092s get the show on it!", "answer": " okay, let me just get a cup of coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh rachel, i know the best coffee house and it\u0092s sooo close.", "answer": " closer than here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  oh, hey, look, i found coffee!  okay, let\u0092s skedaddle.", "answer": " wait, i\u0092m not just gonna drink somebody\u0092s old coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  is he here?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh.  here\u0092s your moisturiser. hi! monica and phoebe: hey!", "answer": " you guys are gonna love meee! okay, check it out, thursday night, five tickets, calvin klein lingerie show, and you guys are coming with me.  okay, i said that out loud right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yes, yes, it\u0092s just that we ah, we kinda all ready, made plans with ross.", "answer": " oh, well okay. well, there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s just that he got this new like home theater dealie, and he wants y'know, us to check it out.", "answer": " hm-mm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " yeah, he\u0092s really excited about it too, he even recorded show times on his answering machine.", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " we\u0092re sorry honey.", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " rach, it\u0092s, it\u0092s ah, it\u0092s not that we don\u0092t want to, really.  are we talking models in their underwear?", "answer": " and heels.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "   ross, did ask us first, and we set that night aside.", "answer": " no, hey, come on, if he asked you first, that\u0092s only fair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " ohhh boy, do i feel bad.", "answer": " oh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " chandler what are you doing?!", "answer": " chandler!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  oh my god!", "answer": " you\u0092re smoking again?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well, actually, yesterday i was smoking again. today, i\u0092m, i\u0092m smoking still.", "answer": " why would you start again after chewing all that quitting gum?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " look, i\u0092m telling you this is just like my parents divorce, which is when i started smoking in the first place.", "answer": " weren\u0092t you nine?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s great, with my luck, that\u0092s gonna be him.", "answer": " him? him, ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hi! uhh, do you guys have plans for the weekend? because i have my sister on hold, and she said that we could use her cabin for the weekend and go skiing. huh? i\u0092m asking you first, right?!. i mean i\u0092m playing by the rules.", "answer": " absolutely, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " chandler! you\u0092re smoking? what are you doing?!", "answer": " hey, shut up!! you\u0092re not my real mom!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hey, can you close that window chandler? my nipples can cut glass over here!", "answer": " wait. really?! \u0091cause mine get me out of tickets.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " look, you guys i just wanna say, i really, really appreciate you spending this time with me. it\u0092s been a pretty hard time right now, so i just wanna say thanks.", "answer": " can somebody else hug him? i have to stay by the window.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh hey, hey, huh, how about this weekend we have a laser disc marathon okay, and maybe a tournament on my new dart board? huh, huh, what do you think?  two days of darts, it\u0092ll be great!", "answer": " it\u0092ll be great for next weekend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no, no, no, this weekend guys!", "answer": " it\u0092ll be great for next weekend. i mean,  it\u0092ll be grrreat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " well, we were um, sorta invited to go skiing, y'know rachel\u0092s sister\u0092s cabin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " so, for the whole weekend?", "answer": " we\u0092re really sorry, but um, she did ask us first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah, that\u0092s okay, i mean if you guys all have to go away for the first weekend i\u0092m alone by myself, y'know then i totally, totally understand.", "answer": " y'know what, i can stay, i\u0092m gonna stay. \u0091cause the last time i went skiing i was to afraid to jump off the chair lift, i just went around and around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " uh, pheebs we kinda need you to drive us all up there in your grandmother\u0092s cab, but y'know what, i\u0092ll stay.", "answer": " noo! i\u0092ll stay. he\u0092s my brother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " what a pity stay?", "answer": " no! we\u0092re gonna have fun. we can make fudge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " pity food? y'know what that\u0092s okay, all right, i don\u0092t need any of you to stay, okay nobody stays.", "answer": " well, then, i might as well offer to stay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  hey, does anybody else feel bad about ross?", "answer": " why? do you think he\u0092s still mad at us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  well he\u0092s probably mad after you called him this morning to borrow his goggles.", "answer": " what? mine aren\u0092t tinted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " chandler!!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " what does the sign say?", "answer": " beam me up jesus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " no, the \u0091no smoking\u0092 sign. there\u0092s no smoking in my grandmother\u0092s cab.", "answer": " okay, well, then, i-i have to go to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no chandler no! no unscheduled stops. you can go when we stop for gas.", "answer": " oh, come on, there\u0092s a rest stop right up there! come on, i really have to goooooooooo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " here we go. okay, brace yourselves.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " ow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  aren\u0092t you gonna go?", "answer": " no. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  no, rachel never pees in public restrooms.", "answer": " well, they never have any paper in there y'know. so my rule is \u0091no tissue, no tuschy.\u0092  well, if everybody\u0092s going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " no, y'know what don\u0092t close it  \u0091cause the... keys.. are in there.", "answer": " oh, no-no-no-no-no-no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " what\u0092s going on?", "answer": "  my lighter\u0092s in there!  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " damn!  the tailpipe\u0092s not hot enough to light this!", "answer": " relax okay, i-i-i can get this open. anybody have a coat hanger?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh i do! op, no, wait a minute, i took it out of my shirt when i put it on this morning.", "answer": " so, if you\u0092re parents hadn\u0092t got divorced, you\u0092d be able to answer a question like a normal person?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " look, i just need a wire something to jimmy it. oh hey, one of you guys give me the underwire from your bra!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " come on! who has the biggest boobs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " please!!", "answer": " whoever has the biggest boobs, has the biggest bra, therefore has the biggest wire.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " no, not getting my bra!", "answer": " if you wanna get back in the car, we need the wire, your call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " okay, monica\u0092s are the biggest.", "answer": " these tiny, little non-breasts?! please, it\u0092s gotta be rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what, no, no, no, mine are deceptively small i mean, i-i-i actually sometimes, st-stuff my bra.", "answer": " all right then, your bra would still be big.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " no, i stuff outside the bra.", "answer": " ladies, ladies, let\u0092s just compromise okay? phoebe, rachel take off monica\u0092s bra.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  chandler, what are you doing? there is a trash can right there.", "answer": " well, i thought if i littered, that crying indian might come by and save us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  okay, there.", "answer": " thank you phoebe, that is very, very generous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " okay, now let\u0092s decide who has the nicest ass.", "answer": "  and there you go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " chandler!!", "answer": " at least let me smoke it to the good part.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay.  oh, no!", "answer": " what, what\u0092s it, what\u0092s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yeah, this has happened before.", "answer": " so you know how to fix it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey, what are you doing here?", "answer": " well, oh just ah, i was just wondering, when you and i split up, did you get the tape that was half the last episode of m*a*s*h and half the hostages coming home?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " ah yeah, but now it\u0092s susan and me in mexico and the hostages coming home.", "answer": " where\u0092s ben?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " he\u0092s sleeping.", "answer": " ahh.  ooh, is this a ah, is this a bad time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " umm, yeah, actually, susan\u0092s gonna be home any minute, it\u0092s kinda an anniversary.", "answer": " oh! i thought you guys got married in uh, january?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " it\u0092s not that kind of anniversary.", "answer": " ah!  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " sooo!! anyway...", "answer": " umm, candles, champagne, yeah anniversaries are great. \u0091cause you know love lasts forever, y'know. nothing like it in this lifetime, money in the bank, so rachel and i broke up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh god, ross i am so sorry.", "answer": " yeah, well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " y'know what, i want to talk to you about this so much, but we should probably do it when we could really get into it, are you free for dinner tomorrow night?", "answer": " oh yeah, i\u0092d love that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh, great! me too.", "answer": " i guess it all started when rachel got this new job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " okay, yeah.  triple a can pick us up.", "answer": " great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " yeah, what town are we near?", "answer": " freemont. west-westmont, ah westburg?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  then why are you answering? do you at least know what route we\u0092re on?", "answer": " yeah, we are definitely on route 27.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " okay.  we are at a rest stop on route 27. okay.  there is no route 27.   okay, either 93 or 76?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, i\u0092m sorry, i always slept in the back when we drove up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay.  hey, can you send somebody up and down 76 and check every rest stop, and, and also 93?  okay!  yeah, no they don\u0092t do that.", "answer": " ugh, okay, well somebody will come and save us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " who? i mean have you seen a car come by here in the last hour and a half? i think we should call ross, maybe he can get a car and come pick us up.", "answer": " no! no, i am not getting in a car with ross, we will just have to live here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " but if...", "answer": " no you guys, i am not getting in a car with him, you\u0092ll have to think of something else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " so the going for help went well?", "answer": " oh yeah, smokey joe here got half way to the highway and collapsed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " then why are you smoking?", "answer": " well it\u0092s very unsettling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " ....right? right? i mean it\u0092s pretty unbelievable y'know, i mean they just took off, took off without even looking back. y'know i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t need them, huh, i\u0092ve got you guys now as friends, you and susan.", "answer": " ah, susan will be so pleased.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": "  717?  where\u0092s 717?  hey, you\u0092ve have more of these for susan right?", "answer": " no. but it\u0092s okay, i\u0092ll just put out pickles or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "   ross, thank god.", "answer": " pheebs? what, why are you whispering?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " listen ross, we ran out of gas, and we don\u0092t know where we are, so we can\u0092t get a tow truck.", "answer": " oh, now you want a favour?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yes, please.", "answer": " well, oh, i\u0092m sorry your car broke down pheebs, but i\u0092m a little too busy with some of my real friends right now, but please call to let me know you got home safely okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "   phoebe, hang on a second.  here, take my car, go pick up your friends.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m not gonna pick them up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " listen, we both know you\u0092re gonna do it \u0091cause you\u0092re not a jerk. okay? so you can either sulk here for a half hour and then go pick them up, or save us both time and sulk in the car.", "answer": " no, rachel doesn\u0092t want me to....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " look, i-i-i am sorry that rachel dumped you \u0091cause she fell in love with that mark guy, and you are the innocent victim in all of this, but don\u0092t punish your friends for what rachel did to you.", "answer": " yeah, you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  phoebe hang on a second ross wants to say something.  what?   you slept with someone else?!", "answer": " we were on a break!!! okay!!  we were, we were...,  yeah. where are you? i\u0092ll find you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " you slept with another woman?", "answer": " oh, you-you\u0092re-you\u0092re one to talk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " okay, done.", "answer": "  what\u0092s \u0091pleh\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " that\u0092s \u0091help\u0092 spelled backwards so that the helicopters can read it from the air!", "answer": " huh. what\u0092s doofus spelled backwards?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  op, op, car! car!!  ugh!!!", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s ross on one of his drives! chandler and joey: hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " what is he doing here?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " he is saving your butt, ah, unless of course i\u0092m stepping on some toes here, in which case i can just mosey on, i\u0092ve got plenty of people to help on the interstate.", "answer": " no! come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " all right!! fine! fine. {ross grabs the gas can he brought along, and walks through joey\u0092s sign destroying it.]", "answer": " arrrghh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh no, now it\u0092s not gonna make any sense!", "answer": "  you guys, what, what do we do about ross who drove all the way up here? what do we do? just like send him back and we\u0092re then gonna go skiing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh, this is horrible, it\u0092s just horrible.", "answer": " guys, do you think we should ask ross to come along?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i know, what about rachel? i mean how are we even gonna ask her?", "answer": " ask me what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " umm, if ah, it might be okay if ross came skiing? chandler, phoebe, and joey: no, i wasn\u0092t gonna ask you that, no.", "answer": " you guys are unbelievable. no! he cannot come.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " it\u0092s horrible.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  oh please, can\u0092t i come to your special, magical cabin?", "answer": " why would you even want to come ross? you\u0092re a horrible skier.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh-oh, hitting me where it hurts, my ski skills.", "answer": " here we go again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i-i can\u0092t handle this, you guys.", "answer": " y'know what, i can handle it, handle\u0092s my middle name. actually it\u0092s the ah, middle part of my first name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " all right pheebs, your cab\u0092s ready.", "answer": " all right, let\u0092s go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " you\u0092re welcome.", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m sorry, were you speaking to me or sleeping with someone else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " we were on a break!", "answer": " y'know ross why don\u0092t you put that on your answering machine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " hey-hey, it\u0092s valid okay? and i\u0092m not the only one who thinks so, monica agrees with me.", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": "  i don\u0092t know.", "answer": " that\u0092s what you said last night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " what i said was, was that i understood. joey\u0092s the one who agreed with you!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " really joey?", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " y'know what, but there is, there is no right or wrong, here.", "answer": " no, i think it\u0092s very obvious who\u0092s wrong here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  look both, joey and monica feel the same way that i do. no-no-no-no.", "answer": " guys, guys, guess who i am?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " hey! hey! hey! hey!! hey!!!  look what you\u0092re doing to chandler!!   yeah, look, we know this is really, really hard for you guys. okay?  you don\u0092t, all right you don\u0092t have to love each other, okay? you don\u0092t, you don\u0092t even have to like each other much right now. but please, you have to figure out a way to be around each other.", "answer": " yeah, and not put us in the middle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " yeah, otherwise, i mean that\u0092s, that\u0092s, that\u0092s just it for us hanging out together. y'know is that what you want?  can you be civil?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " i can.", "answer": " okay. good, all right, let\u0092s get back in the car, \u0091cause it\u0092s freezing, and my chest is unsupported.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh what, wait, wait a second, i mean, what are we doing? who\u0092s going with who?", "answer": " look, you guys, you guys should go.  no, i\u0092m, you, you planned this all out, and i don\u0092t want to ruin it, so you guys should just go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " come on man, you drove all the way up here.", "answer": " no, no, really, i\u0092ve got to take the car back anyway, i\u0092m spending all day tomorrow with ben, it\u0092s fine, no guilt i promise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " all right, we\u0092ll call you when we get back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " maybe we can like go to a movie or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " or, or the rodeo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " that would be great.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " i was being shelly winters from the poseidon adventure.", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": "  ugh.  ross!", "answer": "  hi! sorry i\u0092m late. were you sleeping?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " ahh, nooo!!", "answer": " oh, great! listen, oh i had to get you a whole new battery. i got you the best one i could, \u0091cause that\u0092s not where you want to skimp.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " you\u0092re a genius, ross.", "answer": " yeah, well it came to about $112, but what the hell, just call it an even 110?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay, bye!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " so they ah, they all took off, it was pretty hard watching them go, y'know?", "answer": " yeah, okay, bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}]